[SHUN]
Hey, Auntie.
The boy who was sitting at
that bench, do you know him?
[AUNTIE] Ah. You must
be talking about Mio.
His mother used
to bring him here
when she came to buy bread.
They would stop in quite often
back when he was little.
[SHUN]
Hm.
[ERI]
I'm home!
And I'm totally starving.
Welcome home, dear.
Isn't Suzu coming?
Nah, work.
Mh!
Hey! Eri, don't!
Those are still cooling off.
Worth it though!
[SHUN'S CAT meows]
[CHILD B]
Hey, wait up! That's no fair!
[gasps]
[STUDENTS chattering]
Oh, hey, good morning!
Pretty sure I've seen you
sitting  here a time or tw--
[bicycle bell dings]
[AUNTIE]
Shun!
Could you go grab some veggies?
Oh, um. Unless you're working.
I'm not. What should I pick up?
[SHUN]
Here, from Auntie.
Well, that's nice. You tell her
thank you for us, okay?
Eat this, Shun.
It's good for ya.
[SHUN]
I'm back!
Great. Thanks so much, dear.
[CUSTOMER A] Excuse me!
Could I have, um, a curry?
I'll get my apron.
[AUNTIE]
Please! Thanks, honey!
Coming up!
[GUEST D] 'Scuse me.
Do you know where we check in?
Oh, I've got you.
Just take a seat for now.
I can show ya to your room
in a minute or two, 'kay?
Welcome, boys!
[SHUN]
Who was this for?
It's mine.
[CUSTOMER C]
Heya! Can we order now?
Uh-huh!
[sighs]
[SHUN]
Uh, hey, you! Hold up!
Listen, we made too much bread.
In case you're hungry?
No, not really.
Oh! Uh, no big deal.
It is late, huh?
Wanna take it for later?
Wait, are you giving me that?
Huh? Yeah. I was-- I mean, yes.
That's a very kind
gesture. Thanks.
Not at all, don't mention it.
Welcome home, Shun.
Hey.
Man, this rain came
outta nowhere, huh?
[AUNTIE]
Glad you made it back.
Thanks, Auntie.
[AUNTIE]
Oh, Mio came by earlier.
He left that to
thank us for the bread.
It's a cutting from a
flower his mother grew.
Ah.
[AUNTIE] I hear that Mio
lost his mother recently.
[gasps]
[AUNTIE] It was always
just the two of them,
so now he's alone.
Poor boy isn't even out
of high school yet.
He must be lonely.
[MIO'S MOTHER]
Well, Mio. I'm about to cook.
What should I make?
Curry!
We already had curry.
Yesterday and the day before,
too. Anything else?
Uh.
I want... crab!
Oh. Is today a no-money day?
[MIO'S MOTHER] No, it's fine.
We're having crab.
For real?
Uh-huh!
[MIO laughs]
Hooray!
Krab with a "k" anyway.
[MIO] Thanks for the meal!
Let's dig in!
[MIO'S MOTHER]
This krab is....
Ah! It's yummy!
[MIO'S MOTHER]
Yeah! It really is, huh?
[MIO]
Uh-huh! I'm havin' seconds!
[MIO'S MOTHER]
Go for it! We've got plenty!
[footsteps]
[SHUN]
Mind if I join?
Thanks.
And thank you for the flower.
Sure.
[SHUN]
Hey, so, when you sit here,
are you watching for something?
No, I just sit.
[SHUN] Must get lonely,
always here on your own.
What?
[SHUN]
Huh? Oh, sorry, I--
You're the one who's
always watching me!
It's creepy, okay?
What you're doing is creepy.
[CLASSMATE A] Doesn't Hashimoto
seem kinda femm-y to you guys?
Oh, yeah, totally!
What's your point? Ya think
he's a homo or somethin'?
[CLASSMATE B] Crap, ya think?
I sit right next to him!
[CLASSMATE A]
Better watch out.
[CLASSMATE C] Hope he
doesn't try to hit on me.
[CLASSMATES laughing]
You're awake.
Suzu, what happened?
[ERI]
Hm? 'Bout time, ya bum.
Hate to break it to ya,
but you collapsed again.
Huh? Really?
Oh. Here.
Okay. Did something happen?
Nothing comes to mind.
Thanks, Suzu.
Sorry for the trouble.
[SHUN sighs]
[ERI]
What's on your mind?
I was just wondering what
makes us all so afraid
of two men or two
women being together.
All the things we could fear in
this world and we pick love.
[SHUN'S CAT meowing]
[MIO]
Hey, what's that?
Huh? It's just some work.
I heard that you're in the
middle of writing a novel.
Yeah.
But this isn't the
actual manuscript,
it's more like outlining
and brainstorming, uh...
Not that it actually matters.
[MIO] What I said was
awful. I'm so sorry.
Huh? Uh, why are
you apologizing?
I was the one who came
up and bothered you--
[MIO]
With Mom gone,
everyone seems to think
they know how I feel.
They see me as this
pathetic, lonely vessel
for their goodwill, and their
pity makes it all worse.
I'm sick of having people
try to console me.
And I thought... that was
what you were doing.
Well, you were wrong!
[gasps]
Look, um...
Honestly, I walked up
'cause I was interested.
Or curious,. I mean--
I guess maybe I just
needed a pretext.
[MIO]
Well, that's dumb.
Why would you even
need a pretext?
Oh, wait, were you flirting?
[MIO]
If you were...
...I don't mind.
[ERI] Hey, Shun!
About our plans for dinner--
Oh, my! Oh, my, oh, my!
What brings your beautiful
face back, huh?
Somethin' tells me you
didn't come for the bread.
[SHUN]
Eri!
Oh! That reminds me!
[ERI chuckles]
[BOY A]
Charge!
[MOTHER A laughing]
[MIO]
Shun.
[SHUN]
Hm?
[MIO] Just making sure
that's your name.
[SHUN] Yeah, it's spelled
with the kanji for "horse."
I'm Mio.
You spell it with the kanji for
"bearing fruit" and "center."
Oh, yeah?
[MOTHER A] Would you like
anything special, honey?
[BOY A]
Curry?
[MOTHER A]
Yeah, sure!
[BOY A]
Curry! Curry!
[BOY A, MOTHER A]
Curry! Curry! Curry!
[MOTHER A laughs]
I've gotta say, Shun...
...you kinda suck at fishing.
[ERI]
Wait, what? Where's the fish?
[SHUN] I don't know,
they weren't biting.
Hey, uh, Shun?
I need to start
heading home, so...
The hell're you talking about?
You're not going till
you've had dinner.
[MIO]
Huh?
[SUZU]
Mh-hm!
[ERI]
All right!
And with that...
[ALL chattering]
We're grateful for this meal.
Good work, Mio,
this all looks great!
Thanks. I did a lot of
helping out at home.
Huh, I see.
[AUNTIE]
Here you are, sweetie.
[MIO]
Thanks so much.
We've tried to teach this one
a few things, but he's hopeless.
What even is this?
You don't have to eat it.
Just so ya know, Mio,
Shun's been all
sorts'a concerned
about your wellbeing lately.
[SHUN] Why would you say that?
Mind your own business!
[ERI]
I said it 'cause it's true!
Sorry about the noise,
don't pay any mind.
We never asked,
do you like curry?
Uh, yeah. I like--
[ERI]
Mh-hm...
So cute!
Hey! Either shut your
mouth or stuff it!
[ERI] What, you think I won't
talk with my mouth full?
[SHUN]
Eri, will you please--?
[ERI]
Oh, babe! Pass me some chicken!
[SUZU]
Sure.
[SHUN]
Are you even listening?
[ERI]
I'm really, really not.
[SHUN] Why did you have to
pick tonight to be yourself?
[AUNTIE] My, Suzu, your
potato salad is delicious!
[SUZU] You think so?
I'm glad to hear it.
[MIO]
Ugh... I ate too much.
[SHUN]
Yeah, you were puttin' it away.
[MIO]
Shun.
[SHUN]
Hm?
[MIO] I'm moving tomorrow...
to an orphanage on the mainland.
Huh? Tomorrow?
Well, um, I need
your number, then.
Where's-Where's your phone?
[MIO]
I don't have one.
I'm 17. I'm too young to
make my own choices.
But if you want, I can call
you when I get there.
Would that be okay?
[ERI]
Hey, Professor!
Why don't'cha give
me a hand here?
[SHUN] Would you please
stop calling me that?
Makes me feel like I should be
giving a lecture somewhere.
[ERI]
You good?
[SHUN]
What's it to you?
You're about to flutter off to
your private love nest with Suzu
and live your dream or whatever.
I'm sorry, did we do
something wrong?
Are we hoarding
all the happiness
for ourselves, Professor?
[SHUN] Just shut up and
get outta here already!
[sighs]
[ERI] Say, the next tenant's
s'posed to show up
any minute, right?
Wait, you serious?
That's news to me!
Auntie wanted to bring in
another pair of hands
to help out around here.
[groans] Whatever, I don't care.
[MIO]
Shun? You asleep?
Been a while.
[CAT A meows]
[SHUN]
Mio?
Hey. Good to see ya.
Uh! Hold on, does this mean
that the new tenant is you?
[MIO]
Mh-hm.
You're gonna be living here?
Sure am! I'm 20,
I can live where I want.
And Eri told me how to make
myself useful around here,
so yeah.
I never forgot about you, Shun.
I like you. And now that I'm
back, you can like me!
Huh?
--[SUZU crying]
--[ERI laughs]
Wow. Way to go, Romeo!
[SHUN]
Shut up!
[ERI] This property comes
with some perks, huh?
Aren't you supposed
to be moving out?
[MIO chuckles]
Stop your giggling!
It encourages her! Gah!
[ERI, SUZU]
Congratulations!
[MIO]
Thank you!
[SHUN] Why must my
suffering be endless?!
[MIO]
Are these flowers...?
From the cutting you gave me?
Yeah, they are.
I planted them and they sprouted
right up, just like you.
I have gotten a lot
taller, haven't I?
This is a joke, right?
Mio, this life isn't--
You have to think about this.
I've had three years
to think about this.
[SHUN]
Yeah?
Well, maybe you should've
thought longer.
[MIO]
Maybe you're right.
'Kay, so...
[MIO] Shun, there's no need
to overthink this, okay?
I wanted to be with you.
That's why I'm back.
[SHUN gasps]
Wait a sec!
I'm kinda hungry.
You're what?
Seriously? Now?
[SHUN] So, yeah.
Let's go get some food.
Wait, really?!
Hang on a minute. Shun!
[SHUN]
Oh, that's right.
Welcome back home, Mio.
I, uh... Forgot
to say it sooner.
Right.
[MIO]
Good to be back.
Hey, Mom. Hey, Dad. It's me.
How are you today?
[door opens]
[MIO]
I'm home!
[sighs] It's so cool in here.
Hey, why haven't you eaten
your breakfast yet?
[MIO]
Makin' any progress?
[SHUN groans]
[SHUN]
No. Not at all.
[MIO]
Uh.
Well, hey. Best of luck.
[SHUN chuckling]
[SHUN gasps]
Did you manage to get some?
Uh.
The cooling patches?
Ah! I forgot! Sorry!
I've gotta head to work now,
but I promise I'll pick
them up on my way home!
[AUNTIE]
Another job, eh?
[MIO]
Yup. I'll be back this evening.
See ya later!
[AUNTIE]
Here you are, Mio.
[MIO]
Got it.
Hey, sorry to keep you waiting.
Here's your braised pork belly.
And here's your tofu stir-fry.
[YOUNG WOMAN A]
Live here on the island, kiddo?
Wait, "kiddo"?
Yeah, I sure do.
[YOUNG WOMAN B]
Aww, a local!
And what's your name?
Chibana! Nice to meet you!
And how old?
I'm 20.
[YOUNG WOMEN]
So young!
[YOUNG WOMAN B]
So, do you have a girlfriend?
[YOUNG WOMAN A]
Aw, look, he's blushing!
[YOUNG WOMEN]
So cute!
Shun, the bath is free!
I'm just gonna go
straight to sleep.
[MIO]
Yeah?
Well, in that case, do you
mind if I join ya tonight?
[SHUN]
What? Of course you can't.
Aww. Why not?
You're being way too forward.
You need to use your head, Mio.
Just think before you act.
[MIO]
Mommy!
[gasps]
Mio, you made these
all by yourself?
[MIO] I sure did!
Was I a very big help?
[MIO'S MOTHER]
Mh-hm! This is great!
You were an enormous he... help.
[MIO]
Try 'em, try 'em!
[MIO'S MOTHER]
Okay, here goes!
Mmm! It's delicious!
Thank you so much, Mio!
[MIO]
You're welcome, Mommy!
You're still awake, huh?
[SHUN]
Yeah.
[ERI]
Mio!
I'm coming over tonight.
Is there anything in particular
ya wanna have for dinner?
[MIO]
Curry.
[ERI]
You do love your curry.
So... what're the deets
on your new life
with Professor Loveypants?
[MIO]
Uh, there's not much to say.
[SHUN]
Oh, you're here.
[ERI]
'Sup, ya arrogant jerk?
[SHUN]
What'd I do?
[ERI]
Take a guess.
You need to actually
spend time with him.
What gives?
Are ya pretending to be
too busy? So lame!
[SHUN]
I am hardly pretending!
When you supposed
to send that in by?
[SHUN]
Yesterday.
[MIO gasps]
[SHUN] If I ship it
tomorrow, I'll make it.
Hate to break it to ya,
but I don't think you will.
You sure are a busy guy.
[SHUN]
Well, so are you.
Huh?
[SHUN]
With your customers.
Oh, at the cafe?
That doesn't really compare.
I saw. You're a real
hit there, "kiddo."
[SHUN yelps]
What the hell's your
problem? That really--!
[ERI]
Oh, Mio!
[SUZU] Care for a donut?
They're fresh from the fryer.
Know what? Don't mind if I do.
Hey! Eri! Slow it down!
You already had a bunch at home!
I can't help it; your
donuts are just so good.
[SUZU sighs]
Fine.
You two sure get along well.
Of course we do.
Suzu's actually kind-hearted.
And not just some dour
little troll. Right, Shun?
Why are you like this?
[ERI]
Ya finish your thing?
Yeah. Gonna make a quick
trip to the mainland.
Like right now?
What do you need there?
[SHUN]
To ship this by air.
Oh. Well, have a good trip.
Mio, you should maybe,
I don't know, go with him?
[gasps] Uh, well, I would,
but I'm needed at the café.
Nah, it's fine!
Me and Suzu can fill in
for you, no problem, right?
[SUZU]
Huh? Oh! Sure! You two have fun!
[MIO]
Um, okay.
Here.
For a job well done.
Thank you.
[SHUN]
What's with that?
[MIO gasps]
[SHUN]
The hat.
Oh. I have a hard time with
eye contact and strangers.
And the mainland's crowded.
Huh? What're you talkin' about?
You do fine with
customers at the cafe.
Yeah, I do.
But it's something I've
had to work real hard at.
Wow, I had no clue.
You don't mess around, do you?
[MIO]
Heh. I guess not!
[SHUN] Bet you could find
yourself a girlfriend easy
if ya tried.
Seems like such a waste to me.
[MIO]
Wha--?
Hey. What does that mean?
'Kay, I'm going to the airport.
How' bout you?
I'll catch up later.
[inaudible]
[MIO]
Um, pardon.
But could I ask you
if you like men?
I think you're a bit
young for me, mate.
Oh, no! I-- That...
isn't the reason I asked you.
This guy... Well,
he held my hand once.
And he's been in my
head ever since.
I don't know much about
this stuff, though.
So I just...
I was hoping maybe I could
ask you some things?
You give me a call, son.
Nothing harder than a soda
for you though, yeah?
[phone buzzing]
[SHUN]
Mio? Where are you?
[MIO]
You think I'm stupid.
Like some kind of worked-up kid.
You think I came back
here without thinking.
But I am not a kid.
And you are the only
thing I can think about.
Because I love you, Shun.
But... I need to know.
Do you feel the same?
Are you glad I came back?
Do you want me to go?
Mio! Where are you?
[MIO]
In Sakurazaka by Mimi's bar.
[SHUN]
I'm on my way to you, okay?
Don't leave.
[CLASSMATE A] Doesn't Hashimoto
seem kinda femm-y to you guys?
[CLASSMATE B]
Oh, yeah, totally!
[CLASSMATE C]
What's your point?
Ya think he's a homo
or somethin'?
[CLASSMATE A]
Better watch out.
[CLASSMATE C] Hope he
doesn't try to hit on me.
[CLASSMATES laughing]
[SHUN]
Mio.
[MIO] These feelings didn't come
out of nowhere, Shun, I--
I thought you liked me, too.
I came back here for you.
So why tell me to
find a girlfriend
when you know that
you're what I want?
[SHUN]
C'mon.
Appreciate it.
[HOTEL STAFF A]
Thank you very much, sir.
Breakfast will be served...
[GUEST A] Hey. Take
a look at those two.
[GUEST C]
What? At the front desk?
[HOTEL STAFF A] Oh,
and checkout will be at 10 am.
[GUEST B]
Oh, no. He saw me looking!
[GUEST C]
Shh.
[HOTEL STAFF A]
And that's it.
Here's your room key.
You can take the
elevator to your right.
[SHUN]
Got it.
Huh? Uh, wait.
Hey, Shun? Will you
please talk to me?
Sh-Shun. What are--?
[SHUN]
You should never have come back.
[MIO]
Huh?
You don't want this, Mio.
You should just forget me
while you still can.
You would be happier
with a girl.
I don't...
I don't want to hold you back,
but... but I can't let go.
[SHUN]
Mind if I ask?
Have you ever slept
with a girl before?
Uh. Yeah. I have.
[SHUN]
Me, too.
[MIO]
You're able to?
[SHUN]
More or less.
Although I've never
actually done it with a guy.
Huh? Never? Why not?
'Cause I've never told
a man I wanted to.
All the guys I've
liked were my friends.
Better to say nothing than
watch it all go to hell.
[SHUN sighs]
Oh. Right.
I did make the first
move with you, though.
Couldn't leave you alone.
Shun! Let's make love now!
Huh?
Look, I haven't slept
in about three days.
Well, sleep after!
This is just too sudden, okay?
It isn't gonna work.
Wha--? C'mon,
it'll work if we try!
Hey, Shun! I've been wai--
[SHUN]
Oh. Rice balls. Thank you.
[MIO]
Aww. Dammit.
Why'd you have to
fall asleep on me?
Dumbass!
[SAKURAKO]
Shun?
Wake up. They're ready for us.
Wow. You look great.
Hey. This is real, Shun.
We'll be married soon.
Is that okay?
I need you to be sure.
[gasps]
[MIO]
Shun.
[MAN A] Don't worry,
Mom's gonna love you.
[WOMAN B]
You think?
So can we have sex toni--?
[SHUN]
Nope.
Huh?!
[SHUN]
Could you keep it down?
You're scaring the fish.
What's the deal?
Don't you wanna?
[SHUN]
I do.
[MIO]
I love you, Shun.
[SHUN]
I love you, too.
Now would you go
to work already?
Could'ja say that again first?
[SHUN]
Nope. Not happening.
[MIO]
Aw, why not? C'mon, Shun!
Go, you'll be late.
[MIO] I will, I will.
C'mon, just once?
[SAKURAKO]
Shun!
It's been quite a while.
Huh?! Hey, who is she?
She's an old childhood friend.
And your fiancée, remember?
[SHUN]
Former fiancée.
How'd you know I was here?
And why are you here anyway?
I would think that'd be obvious.
I came because you need
to come back home.
I'm back from the post office--
[SHUN]
Hey. There you are.
My name's Sakurako.
We sort of met earlier.
Uh, my name's Chibana. Hi.
So how long have you
and Shun been friends?
Oh, well...
[SHUN]
He's not my friend.
It's like I've been telling you.
Mio's my lover.
That all for me?
[MIO]
Uh, yeah?
[SHUN]
Cool. Let's see it.
[MIO]
What was that?
[SHUN]
What was what?
Oh, would you have
preferred "boyfriend"?
[MIO gasps]
No! That's not it at all!
Stop playing dumb!
Were you two really engaged?
I broke it off ages ago,
and cut off my whole
family in the process.
[MIO]
Oh. I see.
[sighs]
Something wrong?
My family wants me to come
back for a visit. Soon.
[SHUN] But that's easier
said than done.
I'm taking a bath.
[MIO]
Okay.
[SAKURAKO] Do you have
time to spare today?
[MIO yelps]
Yeah. I guess.
[SAKURAKO]
Where's Shun?
[MIO]
He's busy working. Prob'ly.
Very well.
In that case, I suppose
you'll have to do.
Huh?
I'm happy to give you
a tour of the island,
but it's mostly just
ocean and mountains.
Then I'd rather you
showed me the mountains.
[MIO]
Yeah? Do you not like the sea?
I live in a port town,
so I've seen it enough.
[SAKURAKO]
So...
Yes?
[SAKURAKO] Have you and
Shun... slept together?
I guess that's a "no."
He's better than
you might imagine.
Gentle. Considerate.
All this time and he still
hasn't managed to...
You really should do it already.
[MIO]
Sakurako! Hey, uh...
Sorry to ask, but did you come
here to get back with Shun?
That's what you think?
No, perish the thought.
It's like you haven't heard
a word I've said.
[SAKURAKO] I'm here because his
father's health is failing.
I sent a letter.
Didn't he get it?
Yeah, and he read it,
but is it that bad?
Is he running out of time?
[SAKURAKO]
If he doesn't go now...
If he doesn't see him soon...
...I don't think he'll
ever see him again.
[MIO] I have to ask. Why did
you decide to marry Shun?
[SAKURAKO]
Because he said it was okay.
Even though you knew
he could never love a woman?
You did know. You had to.
[TEAM chattering]
Or ten. Hell, let's
take a quick nap.
Wouldn't that be nice?
[SHUN]
Couldn't you just hand it to me?
Are you really not
gonna tell him?
[SHUN]
'Course not. Why would I?
[SAKURAKO]
Who knows?
It might actually
work out this time.
It's just impossible.
Nothing's impossible, Shun.
But if you don't tell him,
then it may as well be.
You have to take the chance.
[SAKURAKO]
Gather your courage and try.
[SHUN] You don't understand,
and you never will.
[SAKURAKO]
You're a novelist, Shun.
You can write from anywhere.
So come back home
this one time, please.
[SHUN]
Don't wanna.
Hey, guys. I cut up some
watermelon for ya.
[SHUN] I certainly don't feel
like coming home now.
I mean, what're you even doing?
Why would you barge in on
me all the way out here?
You should go and mind your
own family's business.
This doesn't have anything
to do with you anymore.
Shun! You need to
take that back!
[slap]
You selfish child.
I didn't realize you
were this stupid.
[MIO] Hold on! No, please.
Sakurako, wait!
Come on! We need to
go after her, Shun!
[SHUN]
I've got you now.
So why would I ever
go back to them?
You have me?
You are all I need.
[MIO]
Are you--?
It's not possible that
you're trying to use me
as an excuse to run from this?
No, of course not!
[MIO]
Shun!
If he dies, you can
never see him again.
Never mind me. I'm okay.
Just go home.
[MIO]
Uh.
I'm okay.
[meows]
[SHUN]
Don't you start.
[SHUN'S FATHER] First you run
off, abandoning your bride,
and now you're telling us
that you like men?
What is wrong with you?
How can you do this now?!
[SHUN'S MOTHER]
It's not true. Is it, Shun?
Just say it's not true!
[SAKURAKO]
You selfish child.
I didn't realize you
were this stupid.
[MIO]
Never mind me. I'm okay.
Just go home.
[SHUN]
Dammit!
[SHUN'S MOTHER] Here, I'll
take one of the both of you.
C'mon, give me some smiles!
[SHUN'S FATHER]
So serious.
[SHUN'S MOTHER laughs]
It's all right though.
They're still adorable.
[SAKURAKO] Hey, Auntie!
We got that sweet rice drink!
Oh, yeah? Get some amazake  ?
And the two of you are sharing,
right? That's lovely.
[SAKURAKO]
Oh, and, Auntie, Uncle?
We talked, and once
we're all grown up,
I'm gonna be Shun's wife!
[SHUN'S FATHER laughs]
Is that so? Well done, son.
[SAKURAKO]
I really am!
I know because he promised.
Right? Tell 'em!
Right. As long as
it's you, it's fine.
[MIO]
Sakurako!
You really shouldn't be
out here all by yourself,
especially not at night, okay?
It's dangerous!
Let's head back.
Please, I'll take you.
[SAKURAKO]
You should've told him, Mio.
If you had told Shun that
you needed him here,
he would've stayed
without a second thought.
So why didn't you?
You can't want him
to leave you behind--
why not say how you feel?
Come on.
I mean, I could ask you
the same thing, couldn't I?
[SAKURAKO]
Except I did say it!
I wanted to be with him,
even if he could never love me.
I told him.
[MIO]
Sakurako.
I don't want to hide
him away from his life.
I might not be the last
person he loves either.
That choice is his...
and he has to make it.
No, you can't think that way!
Because whether he sees it
or not, Shun needs you!
[MIO]
I'm... sorry.
Why are you apologizing?
You don't know me.
We're strangers.
[MIO]
I know you love him.
I know just what
that looks like.
I know because I love him, too.
So that's why... I'm sorry.
Dammit, Mio.
If only Shun were seeing
some kind of lowlife.
This'd be so much easier.
[MIO]
When I was little,
Mom always said that
if I came here alone,
I'd be swept away.
Swept away?
Yeah. To the other side.
She's been there
for a long time now.
But I still miss her.
I'm still sad.
So if Shun's parents
are asking for him...
...then I want him
to go and see them.
[MIO'S MOTHER, MIO laughing]
[MIO'S MOTHER]
You're so fast, Mio!
I sure am!
Try to keep up, Mommy!
I'll do my best!
[MIO]
Actually, could you carry me?
[MIO'S MOTHER]
Okay! Hyup!
[BOTH]
Squeeze!
You smell good. I love you.
[SHUN]
Mio!
Hey, why didn't you answer
your phone when I called you?
Didn't you know I'd be worried?
Sorry, uh, I don't have it.
Think I left it in my room.
[SHUN] Thus defeating the
purpose of a cellphone.
So how did it go?
Is Sakurako all right?
[MIO]
I took her back to her inn.
Where is she staying?
[MIO]
She said not to come by today.
[SHUN sighs]
[SHUN]
You must be exhausted.
Huh?
[SHUN] Sorry for dragging
you into my mess.
Oh. That's all right.
[MIO]
But when someone cares for you,
maybe try not to
crush their spirits.
I mean, you handled that
as horribly as you
possibly could've, Shun.
Stop being so selfish
and grow up.
[MIO laughs]
Aw. I'm kiddin'.
Did I getcha?
[SHUN]
I really am sorry.
[MIO]
Aww.
[CAT A meows]
[SAKURAKO]
Well, you've worn me down.
All of my patience is spent.
[SHUN]
Sakurako, I--
Goodbye forever.
Have a pleasant life.
Since I'm an outsider
to your family,
I beg your pardon.
[MIO] Uh. Now, now.
Let's stop there, 'kay?
You know he didn't
mean that, Sakurako.
[SAKURAKO] Please just go home.
Your father's health is--
Failing, I know.
I did read the letter.
[SAKURAKO]
I see.
Hey, Shun? Kiss me
farewell, would you?
Huh?!
[SHUN]
What the hell--?
Just do it, and then
I can give up on you!
Come on, Shun!
You've never done it before,
not even when we were engaged!
[gasps]
[SAKURAKO] He's better
than you might imagine.
Gentle. Considerate.
[SHUN sighs]
[SHUN]
Sakurako, I--
[horn blares]
I... I--
I wasn't asking for a kiss
from you, you stupid jerk!
[MIO]
Sorry!
Shun might've been cool with it,
but I'm young and possessive.
See ya later, Sakurako!
[SAKURAKO] I'm never coming back
to this island. It's all yours!
[SHUN] So passes the
storm of the century.
Let's head back.
I need some sleep.
[MIO]
Hey.
Ow, that really hurt, Mio!
[MIO]
Shut up!
You should've said "I can't"
as soon as she asked
for that kiss!
If I hadn't stepped in like
I did, you'd've done it.
You'd've kissed her
right in front of me!
[SHUN]
Eh? Wait, what?
I am so frickin'
over this! Dumbass!
[SHUN]
Huh...?
Hey, Mio.
[MIO]
Shut up and leave!
[SHUN]
It's dinnertime.
[MIO]
I'm not hungry!
[SHUN] Auntie? Mio isn't
gonna eat until later.
[AUNTIE]
Oh, honey. Did you have a fight?
Well...
[AUNTIE laughs]
[AUNTIE] Well, then maybe
you should eat later, too?
[SHUN grumbles]
[SHUN]
Hey.
I'm gonna come in.
[SHUN] Mio, what's up?
You still sulking?
[SHUN sighs]
Really, what is it with you?
I feel like I make
you cry all the time.
You do. Go away.
Give up. I'm still mad--
Sorry, but I can't.
Not when you're this close
and in need of comfort.
[MIO gasps]
[MIO]
Hold on!
[SHUN]
Huh? What is it?
We're doing this right!
Clothes off!
[SHUN]
Listen.
Are you... Are you really
sure you wanna do this?
Of course I am. What's wrong?
[SHUN] I just don't want you
to do anything you'll regret.
[MIO]
Shun, I'm not gonna--
Why would you say that now?
Clothes off. This is happening.
[SHUN gasps]
[SHUN] Hey, would you--?
Can you top?
[MIO gasps]
I don't know, Shun.
I'm not sure I could
hold out for very long!
You just came, Mio.
Maybe we could
just give it a try?
[MIO] I mean, if it's what
you want, of course.
I guess I'm just nervous.
Well, can you get
over that quickly?
'Cause I'm a bottom.
Plus I already took a bath
and did some other stuff.
What other stuff?
Don't worry about it.
[MIO]
Okay.
I'm gonna put my finger in.
Wait, did you already
prep yourself?
You've gotta teach
me how after this,
then I can do it
for you sometime!
Yes, fine, okay,
whatever! Put it in.
[MIO]
Here goes.
Shun, does it feel okay?
It's so much.
[SHUN]
To one day...
...be with someone I love.
It's not too much is it?
You want me to stop?
[SHUN]
Not ever.
To lie in his arms.
For me, it was a dream
that I never thought
would come true.
[MIO]
You okay?
[SHUN sighs]
[MIO]
Drink?
[SHUN]
No. I'm fine.
Want some tempura?
[SHUN]
Nah. It's all yours.
Are ya sure? Lucky me!
[SHUN] I feel like I never
did a thing for you.
Huh? Sure ya did.
You were great!
[SHUN] I'm not talkin'
about that, genius.
Just so you know,
I really do love you.
More than you know.
More than anything else.
I want to find a way
to prove it to you.
Ya let me eat all this.
Stop. That's not what
I mean, and you know it.
You did something for me.
I thought I only liked girls,
but then I met you,
and I knew I loved you.
And somehow, I knew it
was all gonna be okay.
[SHUN]
Listen, Mio.
[MIO]
Huh?
[SHUN]
I'm gonna go back home.
[MIO]
'Kay.
[AUNTIE] You've really
tidied up, haven't you?
Yeah, it's been comin' along.
Sorry for rushin' off.
Don't fret about it.
Take all the time you need
to care for your father.
And if there's anything I can
do to help, just say the word.
Sure. Thanks, Auntie.
[SHUN]
Mio, what are you doing?
Stop watching me.
What you're doing is creepy.
[MIO laughs]
Just kidding!
Hey, Hokkaido's pretty
chilly, isn't it?
Try not to catch a cold there.
I'll write you. Or call. I do
have a cellphone this time--
Are you good with this?
You know, you could come with--
I'll be gone a while.
Are you just gonna
wait here... like I did?
C'mon, say what you mean.
Mio!
I need you.
So please, come with me.
[MIO]
Of course I will.
I'll go where you go.
I don't wanna be
without you. Not ever.
Well, don't cry about it.
I am not crying!
[MIO]
Hey, Shun? Let's get wet!
Just come with me!
[SHUN]
Ah! Whoa! Hang on!
Mio! Ah! It's freezing!
Yeah, I know, right?
Hey, Shun?
[SHUN]
Uh?
[MIO]
I'm really happy.
Thank you.
[MIO laughing]
[SHUN]
Yeah. Sure.
[MIO]
Come on, just a littel further.
[SHUN]
No! No, we go back!
[MIO laughing]
[MIO]
There.
Mom, Dad, take care
till I get back, okay?
I've gotcha.
Well, we'd better get
a move on. Here.
[SHUN]
All right. You ready?
Hm?
[chuckles]
I'm good to go.
[ERI]
Shun! Mio!
The ferry's gonna
leave without ya!
'Kay!
[SHUN]
Mio? You with me?
[MIO]
Coming!